Guide to the The Review of Contemporary Fiction/Dalkey Archive Press: records, 1980-1990
Department of Special Collections
- Series I: Review of Contemporary Fiction
  - Bukowski / Butor
    - Trapped: Analysis of Resean Aenien - Josee Lambert (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Butor's Rare and. Limited Editions: 1956-1983 -Aubyn (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Book Reviews and Books Received and Annual Index (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Michel Butor: entre la foule et le beros -A. Helbo (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - World Literature Today - Vol. 56 #2 Spring 1982 (photostat) (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Signaux De Fumee - Pour Michel Sicard (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Bokowski: Drain a Last Tired Beer - Challis (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Table of Contents (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Text copy: title page - p.59 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Text copy: pp. 60-118 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Text copy: pp. 119-164 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Text copy: pp. 165-210 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Fiction Issue
    - Correspondence: Acker - Hawkes (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Lane - Tindall (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - The Apocrypha - Pinget (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Armenian Papers - Harry Matthews (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - From Unmaking It: 'Radical Surgery' -Wallace Markfield (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Vito in Europe - Part II - Ann Rower (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - The Corpse Dream of N. Pektor - Thomas McGonigle (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Model Wife - Margaret Mitchell Dukore (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - In Another World - Margaret Mitchell Dukore (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Two Mose Bankes - Gilbert Sorrentino (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - In the Mood - Colleen Dowell (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Don Quixote in America, the Land of Freedom -Kathy Acker (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Excerpts fran Landscapes After the Battle -Goytisolo (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - From Ghost Waves - James McManus (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Unwelcome Words - Paul Bowles (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Three Sketches for a Meta-Myth - Nicholas Mosley (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - From Pignon - Kenneth Tindall (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - From Larva: 'Auto da Fenix - Julian Rios (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Book Reviews: originals (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Book Reviews: copies (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - The Coming of Night - A Brief Introduction -Kathy Acker (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Text Models and Copies (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Text Copy: pp. 1-52 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Text Copy: pp.53-98 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Text Copy: pp.99-156 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Text Copy: pp.157-197 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Text Copy: pp.198-228 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Calvino
    - Correspondence: Alamansi - Joseph (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: La Polla - Migiel (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Marello - Willen (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Table of Contents (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - La Camera Ardente - Harry Matthews (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Calvino' s Combinative Aesthetics: Theory and Practice - Jerry A. Varsava (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - + Zero: Halo Calvino's Minimalist Narratives -Sorel Thompson Friedman (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Man, History, Subject, Object: Calvino in Crisis -John Earl Joseph (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - The Recovery of Mnemonic Meanings in L'entrata inguerra - Franco Ricci (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - A Note on Marcovaldo - Franco La Polla (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Calvino' s Fantastic 'Ancestors': The Viscount, the Baron, and the Knight - Jack Byrne (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Optimism without Illusions - Francesco Guardiani (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Italo Calvino: A Woman, a Moon, the City -Michael Stephens (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Calvino' s Framed Narrations: Writers, Readers, and Reality - Kathryn Hume (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Calvino's Combinatorics - Warren F. Motte, Jr. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - The Fragmentation of Allegory in Calvino's Invisible Cities - Carol P. James (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Form and Formula in calvino's Invisible Cities -Laura Marcello (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Ghosts and Shadows: Reading and Writing in Italo Calvino's If on a Winter's Night a Traveller -Geoffrey Green (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - "Romancing the Reader: Calvino's If On a Winter' s Night a Traveller - Carl D. Malmgren (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Another Book, Another Author: Calvino, Flaubert, Mallarme - Marshall C. Olds (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - The Role of the Reader in Italo Calvino's If On a Winter's Night a Traveller - Ian Rankin (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Calvino on Photography - Constance Pierce (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - The Game of Palomar - George Scalise (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Book Reviews (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Contributor's Notes (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Italo Calvino e le favole Italiane -Guiseppe Caputo (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Text Copy: pp. 1-41 (photograph of Calvino) (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Text Copy: pp. 42-87 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Text Copy: pp. 88-123 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Text Copy: pp. 124-167 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Valenzuela
    - Correspondence: Araujo - Garfield (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Gazarian - Mull (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Orthmann - de Zapata (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Table of Contents (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - My Extraordinary Ph.D.' From Cat-O-Nine-Deaths by Luisa Valenzuela Evelyn Picon Garfield (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Dangerous Words - Luisa Valenzuela (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Dirty Words - Luisa Valenzuela (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - In Search of My Own Backyard - Luisa Valenzuela (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - In Search of My Own Backyard - Luisa Vabenzuela (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - From The Motive - Luisa Valenzuela (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Interview with Luisa Valenzuela - Evelyn Picon Garfield (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Valenzuela's Cat-O-Nine-Deaths - Ann H. Fores (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Female Sexuality in Selected Short Stories by Luisa Valenzuela: Towards an Ontology of Her Work -Marting (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - That Which Resists: The Code of the Real in Luisa Valenzuela's He Who Searches -Emily Hicks (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Luisa Valenzuela's He Who Searches - Margo Glantz (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - The Symbolic, the Imaginary and the Real in Luisa Valenzuela 's He Who Searches - Guillermo Maci (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Valenzuela's 'Other Weapons - Helena Araujo (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Other Weapons': When Metaphors Become Real -Marta Morello-Frosch (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Ritual Transformation in Luisa Valenzuela's 'Ritual of Rejection' - Dorothy S. Mull (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - The Lizard's Tail: Discourse Denatured -Sharon Magnarelli (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - The Sorcerer and Luisa Valenzuela, Double Narrators of the Novel/Biography Myth/History -Marie-Lise Gazarian Gautier (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Luisa Valenzuela's 'Where the Eagles Dwell': From Fragmentation to Holism - Zulima Nelly Martinez (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Van Vogt's Use of Suetonius - Robert Edgeworth (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Book Reviews (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Interview with Luisa Valenzuela (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - The Fruits of Summer -Luisa Valenzuela (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Luisa Valenzuela's 'Little Man, Festo ' - Luisa Valenzuela (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Censorship in Argentina from the Writer's Point of View - Luisa Valenzuela (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Poetry and Short Stories (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - 'Springtime' from Cat-O-Nine-Deaths - Evelyn Picon Garfield (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - The Efficient Cat' from The Efficient Cat -Evelyn Picon Garfield (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Luisa Valenzuela's List (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Brossard
    - Correspondence: Abel - Brossard (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Bryant - Levy (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Lykiard - Woods (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Tentative Visits to the Cemetary: Reflections on My Beat Generation - Chandler Brossard (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - From Come Out with Your Hands Up! -C. Brossard (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Interview with Chandler Brossard -Steven Moore (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Chandler Brossard: An Introduction and Checklist -Steven Moore (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Chandler, WWD, and, Inevitably, Hopefully Not Intrusively, Me - Seynour Krim (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - My Chandler Brossard - John Bowers (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - The 'Passed' White Nero: Brossard and Mailer at the Roots of Hip - William Crawford Woods (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Chandler Brossard - A View fran England -Con Holland-Skinner (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Publishing Big Chan: A Sort of Valentine -Joyce Engelson (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - The Bright Wonderful Surface - Alexis Lykiard (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - The Bold Saboteurs - Edgar Z. Friedenberg (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Of Oatmeal Cookies and, Brossard - Mandy Keifetz (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - The Labors of Yogi - Norman Kelfetz (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Notes on Chandler Brossard as Playwright -Jay Landesman (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - The Masked Centaur: Cultural Ambivalence in The Double View - James R. Lindroth (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Chandler Brossard, Cynic - Jerry H. Bryant (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - The Spanish Scene - Barbara Probst Soloman (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Chandler Brossard: A Critical Study of 'Dirty Books for Little Folks - S. Ramneth (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Dirty Books - John Coyne (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - The Abuses of Enchantment - William Levy (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Raging Joys, Sublime Violations: The Vietnam War in the Fiction of Chandler Brossard -Philip Beidler (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - About Wake Up - Chandler Brossard (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Text Copy: pp. 33-64 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Text Copy:: pp. 193-end (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Issue Format Pieces (photographs, originals, etc.) (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Beckett
    - Correspondence: John O'Brien (editor) with Nicholas Zurbrugg (guest editor) (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Contributors to Editors (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - IntroductIon: Samuel Beckett-The Wider Context -Nicholas Zurbrugg (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Three Extracts frau Dream of Fair to Middling __ - Samuel Beckett (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Dream of Fair to Middling Warren: A Preface and Post-Script - Deidre Bair (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Beckett and Proust - William Burroughs (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - A Footnote to William Borroughs 'Article 'Beckett and Proust' - Nicholas Zurbrugg (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Beckett and Deep Sleep - Robert Lax (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - A Note on Ill Seen Ill Said and A Note on criticism - Michael O'Brien (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Notes on Three Novels by Samuel Beckett -Michael Horovitz (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Island Truancies: The Sauntering of Mercier and Camier - James Liddy (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - What's a Door Doing Here?' A Squint at Beckett's Layered Question -Dom Sylvester Haiedard (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - The Structure of Lessness - Rosemary Pountney (Appendix 1) (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - The Music in Samuel Beckett's Play -Kenneth Gaburo (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Interview with David Warrilo - Nicholas Zurbrugg (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Interview with Philip Glass - Nicholas Zurbnigg (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Interview with Billie Whitelaw - Nicholas Zurbrugg (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - From Characters to Discrete Events: The Evolving Concept of Dramatis Personae in Beckett's Radio Plays - Germaine Baril (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - What Where II: Revision as Recreation -S. E. Gontarski (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - The Anti-Zoom (A Little Polemic Against Metaphor) -Peter Gidal (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - LeWitt in Progress - Rosalind E. Krauss (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Self and Theatricality: Samuel Beckett and Vito Acconci - Paul Taylor (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Waiting for Commercials - Nam June Paik (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - In Memory of Christine Tsingos - Bernard Heidsieck (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Beckett and Proust - Lourdes Castro (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - The New Overbrook The Lost Ones: Story of the Work -Charles Altschul (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Statement on The Lost Ones - Charles Klabunde (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - No Matter. Try Again. Fail Again. Fail Better Tom Phillips (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Poem Sequence for Samuel Beckett - John J. Sharkey (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Parisian Notes - John Taylor (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - They Come': A Fifty Percent Mesostic - John Cage (for N.Z.) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Layout Sheets and Notes for Issue (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Text Copy: pp. 1-54 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Text Copy: pp. 55-107 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Text Copy: pp. 108-160 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Text Copy: pp. 161-176 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Text Copy: pp. 177-end (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Mathews
    - Text Copy: (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Text Copy: Mathews - Watten (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Text Copy: White - Wright (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - For Prize Winners - Harry Mathews (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - A Conversation with Harry Mathews - John Ashbery (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - John Ashbery Interviewing Harry Mathews (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - 'Owen and Phobe: II 'from Cigarettes -Harry Mathews (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Their Masks, Their Lives-Harry Mathews' Cigarettes - Edmund White (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Avez-Vous Lu Harry Mathews? - Georges Perec (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Harry Mathews' Fiction: A Map of Masks -Joseph McElroy (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Permutational Mathews - Warren F. Motte (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Harry Mathews ' The Conversions: In the Net of the Goddess - Thomas Mirkowicz (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - About Harry Mathews' Fiction - Kenneth Koch (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - From 'A Place Apart' - W. C. Bamberger (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Tlooth - Barbara Guest (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Lies Like Truth-The Art of Harry Mathews -Frederick Ted Castle (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Harry Mathews: An Experiment in Presence -Barrett Watten (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Harry Mathews' Selected Declarations of Dependence: Proverbs and the Forms of Authority -Welch D. Everman (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 'Eleusions Truths': Harry Mathews' Strategies and Games - Eric Mottram (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - The Labors of Signifier - Keith Cohen (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - The Genius of Friendship - Hubert Damisch (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - A Brief Note Concerning the Impossibility of Harry Mathews - Jacques Jouet (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Harry Mathews: A Checklist - Bill McPheron (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - The Achievement of Coleman Dowell: A Bibliographical Essay - John Kuehi (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Lesser-Known Contemporary German Authors -Nicholas J. Meyerhofer (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Harry Mathews' Fiction: What Is At Stake? -Joseph McElroy (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Book Reviews and Books Received (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Contributor's Notes (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Drafts for Advertisments and Photographs (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Drafts for Title Page: PHOTOGRAPH (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Text Copy: title page-p. 48 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Text copy: pp. 49-99 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Text copy: pp. 100-153 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Text copy: pp. 154-196 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Text copy: pp. 197-244 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Text copy: pp. 245-272 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Ollier
    - Correspondence: Aas - Knee (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Laabi-Montel (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Noguez - Zadek (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Unknown Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Enigma ou le Double Simulacre - Jean Claude Montel (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Our Musigue, Dix Ans Apres - Christian Rosset (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - La Figure Dans Le Jew D'Enfant -Philippe de la Genardiere (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Topographies - Philippe Boyer (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Sur Les Traces D'un Trauma - A. Khatibi (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - La lecon des incipit - Philippe de la Genardiere (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Une histoire illisible au non de la troisiene personne - Abdelwahab Meddeb (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Ia Theatre De Claude Ollier -Gerhard Goebel-Schihling (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Fuentes
    - Correspondence: Brandt - Fuentes (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Gass-Zeitz (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - The Triple Lunar Goddess and Her Cult in Some of Fuentes' Short Fiction - Janet Perez (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Point of View in the Death of Artemio Cruz: Singularity or Multiplicity Santiago Tejerina-Canal (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Carios Fuentes et le miroir de Malintzin -Marc Nacht (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - A Gallery of Women in Canoe Fuentes' Canter de ciegos - George Gordon Wing (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Magic Realism and Fantastic History: Carlos Fuentes' - Lois Parkinson Zamora (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Odor Motifs in The Death of Artemio Cruz -Genaro J. Perez (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Narrative Complexities in Fuentes' Aura -Chanles F. Dameron (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - 'Chac-Mool': A Journey into the Fantastic -Joseph Tyler (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Fuentes articles (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Books Received (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Schmidt
    - Guest Editor's Note - F.P. Ott (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - A Guest in the Cave of Books - Klaus T. Hofmann (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - On Translating the Unconventional Prose of Arno Schmidt - John E. Woods (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - A Heart of Stone - Arno Schmidt (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Great Cain - Arno Schmidt (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Calculations (I-III) - Arno Schmidt, tr. by F.P. Ott (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Why were they saying such terrible things about Arno Schmidt? - Robert Weninger (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Arno Schmidt: The German Context - Keith Bullivant (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Bestandige Schnoddrigkeiten-'-Arno Schmidt and the Human Voice - Anthony Phelan (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Narrative Technique in the Kuhe in Halbtauer Series - Ulrich Goerdten (tr. by Thomas Hansen) (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - And back. And forth. - Ernst-Dieter Steinwender (tr. by F.P. Ott) (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Some Preliminary Remarks Concerning the Presentation of Page 636 of Zettels Traum -Ernst Krahwehl (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pleasurable=Profitable Playfulness - Horst Denkler (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Producing the 'EG' -Figures of the Readymade Unconscious in Evening Edged in Gold - Kurt Jauslin (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Mystifictional Traces - Suzanne Kretzer (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Moments From the Work of a Faun - Juhian Rios (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Schmidt/Joyce: A Case of Possession -David Hayman (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Schmidt/Joyce: Anatomy of a Misunderstanding -Stefan Gradmann (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Arno Schmidt's Reception of E.A. Poe "-Thomas S. Hansen (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Arno Schmidt: A Select Bibliography - F.P. Ott (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Guest Editor's Note - F.P. Ott (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - A Guest in the Cave of Books - Klaus T. Hofmann(Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - On Translating the Unconventional Prose of A.Schmidt - John E. Woods (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - From 'A Heart of Stone - A.Schmidt (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Great Cain - A. Schmidt (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Tall Grate - A. Schmidt (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Calculations (I-III) - A. Schmidt (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Why Were They Saying Such Terrible Things About Arno Schmidt? - R. Weninger (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Arno Schmidt: The German Context - K. Bollivant (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Bestandige Schnoddrigkeiten - Anthony Phelan (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Narrative Technique in the Kuhe Halbtrauer Stories -Ulrich Goerdten (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - 'And back. And forth' - Ernst-Dieter Steinwender (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Some Preliminary Remarks Concerning the Preservation of Page 636 - Ernst Krawehl (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - 'Pleasurable=Profitable Playfulness -Horst Denkler (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - OLters ' Method: Producing the 'EG' -Kurt Jaushin (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Mystifictional Traces - Suzanne Kretzer (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - "Moments From the Work of a Fauntes. - Juhian Rios (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Schmidt/Joyce: A Case of Possession - Devid Hayman (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Schmidt/Joyce: Anatomy of a Misunderstanding" -Stefan Gradmann (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Arno Schmidt's Reception of E.A. Poe. -Thomas Hansen (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Arno Schmidt: A Select Bibliography - F.P. Ott (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Book Reviews (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Books Received (Corrected Galley) (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Drafts of RCF Covers: Cortazar/Hawkes; Comedy Issue; Claude Simon; Metcalf/Selby; Fiction Issue; Johnson/Rhys; Misterio - Gilbert Sorrentino (Box 35)
    - Moore correspondence: 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Moore/Weinreich correspondence: 1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Book Reviews: Fall Issue 1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Annual Index (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Interview with Regina Weinreich (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Chandler Brossard: An Introduction and Checklist (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Claude Ollier Today: An Introduction - Cecile Lindsay (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Claude Ollier: A Bibliography (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Claude Ollier: A Bibliography (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Interview with Claude Ollier - Cecile Lindsay (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - French Version - Claude Ollier (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - From Mon Double y Malacca - Claude Ohlier (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - from Marrakch Medine - Claude Ollier (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - The Shadow of a Doubt - Paul Louis Rossi (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Child's Play: La Jeu D'Enfant and Beyond - Cecile Lindsay (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Concealed Production in Ollier's First Novel -Leon S Roudiez (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - "Microstructural Intertextuality: Solving Claude Ollier's Enigma - Robin Knee (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Enigma: Or the Double Similacrum - Jean-Claude Montel. (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - 'Our Music', Ten Years After - Christian Posset (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Topographies - Philippe Boyer (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Traces of a Trauma: on Marrakch Medine - Abdelkehi Knatibi (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Claude Ollier and the Death of 'the Orient' in Marrakch Medine - Abdeliatif Laabi (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - The Lesson of the Incipits - Philippe de la Genardiere (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - An Unreadable Story (Une Histoire illisible): In the Name of the Third Person - Abdelwahab Meddeb (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Cahiers d'ecolier and Ollier's Fiction - Irigrid Axmann (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Claude Ollier's Heterogeneous Linguistic Topography of Polymorphic Experience - Anna Otten (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - The Theater of Claude Ollier - Gerbard Goebel-Schilling (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Text Copy: pp. 7-44 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Text Copy: pp. 45-92 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Text Copy: pp.93-l43 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Fuentes in Action - Debra A. Castillo (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Canoe Fuentes: A Bibliography (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Travails with Time: An Interview with Canoe Fuentes -Debra Castillo (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Mother and Doctor - Carlos Fuentes (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Carlos Fuentes: Good Twice Over - Gabriel Garcia Marquez (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - A Translator' s Recollections - Margaret Sayers Peden (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - The Question of Carlos Fuentes - Octavio Paz (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - The Triple Lunar Goddess in Aura and 'In a Flemish Garden -Janet Perez (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Point of View in The Death of Artemo Cruz: Singularity or Multiplicity? - Santiago Tejerina-Canal (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Carlos Fuentes and Maiintzin's Mirror - Marc Nacht (Box 37, Folder 13)